https://www.mr-s-leather.com/help/privacy-policy

Menu New / HotNew ItemsTit Toys - 30% OffPump Sale - 20% OffSaleGift CardFace MasksHoliday Gear Mr. S Leather Logo GearBondage / BDSMBondage RestraintsGagsBlindfoldsCollars / LeashesBondage Hoods / MuzzlesLeatherRubberNeopreneSpandexMuzzlesBDSM MasksSleepsacksStraitjacketsSuspensionFetters USAChastityFloggers / WhipsPaddles / Canes Rope / TapeSpreader BarsHandcuffsIron RestraintsLocks / AccessoriesSex ToysAss Play* Hankey's Toys* Crackstuffers* Square Peg Toys - Silicone* Oxballs* Perfect FitButt PlugsCock ExtendersSuction Cup DildosDouble-Ended DildosDildo/Buttplug HarnessesVibes / ProstateRealistic CocksVac U LockInflatable DildosVixen - SiliconePVC / VinylAnal BeadsMetal ToysDepth ToysLube / Boner PillsAnal Douche / Enema ToysCock / BallStretch Cock / Ball ToysMetal Cock RingsMetal Stretchers / WeightsLeather CockstrapsCock / Ball Torture (CBT)OxballsElectro-PlayPower BoxesButt ToysCock & Ball ToysMore ToysWires & AccessoriesViolet WandsElectrastimE-Stim SystemsMyStimFleshjack / StrokersPumpingSoundingTit ToysMedicalGloves / CondomsFucking MachinesFuck SheetsSex Slings / Furniture* Square Peg ToysBeginnerIntermediateAdvancedPlugsFistingCocksDepthPuppy Play & TailsAll Square Peg Toys* Oxballs* Perfect Fit* NexusLeatherHarnessesJocksShorts / KiltsPants / ChapsShirts / VestsBelts / Sam BrowneSuspendersCaps / GlovesJacketsBootsWristbands / ArmbandsAccessoriesRubberJocks / ShortsPants / ChapsShirts / HarnessesSuits / BondageSocks / GlovesAccessoriesNeopreneJocks / ShortsShirts / VestsSuits / BondageHarnessesAccessoriesSport / StreetOpen Ass GearJockstrapsBriefs / TrunksSocksFace MasksHarnessesSingletsTees / TanksShortsJackets / HoodiesAccessoriesLimited Edition Pins* Mr. S Leather Logo Gear* CellBlock13* Nasty Pig* Boxer Barcelona* Locker Gear* Sk8erboyPuppy ParkNeoprene Puppy HoodsNeoprene MuzzlesLeather Puppy HoodsLeather MuzzlesPuppy Collars / LeashesPuppy Tails Puppy MittsTees / AccessoriesHelpContact Us / Customer SupportShipping FAQReturn PolicyRewards ProgramPrivacy PolicyCommunityVisit Our StoreCustomer Experience
Account
Home
Help
Privacy Policy
Help
Contact Us / Customer Support Shipping FAQ Return Policy Rewards Program Privacy Policy Community Visit Our Store Customer Experience
Privacy Policy Confidentiality is a cornerstone of Mr. S Leather. We are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers.
All orders from Mr. S Leather are shipped in plain packaging using a return address of "MSL"
Unlike many online businesses, we DO NOT AND WILL NOT sell or rent access to customer mailing lists or databases to other companies. We WILL NOT share ordering information with anyone outside the company.
We have taken extensive measures to make our ordering systems secure. All exchange of personal data takes place in a secure environment and with high level encryption. Encryption is also used for the storage of your sensitive data.
For more information, please see our full Privacy and Cookie Policy
